The Terror is Real
The Poughkeepsie Tapes is a horror, mystery, crime
film directed by John Erick Dowdle.
When hundreds of videotapes showing torture, murder and dismemberment are found in an abandoned house, they reveal a serial killer's
decade-long reign of terror and become the most disturbing collection of evidence homicide detectives have ever seen.
Cheryl Dempsey, played by Stacy Chbosky.
Edward 'Ed' Carver, played by Ben Messmer.
Felton Lewis, played by Lou George.
Leonard Schway, played by Ivar Brogger.
Simon Alray, played by Michael Lawson.
Alice Endrisart, played by Amy Lyndon.
The Poughkeepsie Tapes is a 2007 American pseudo-documentary horror film written, directed, and
edited by John Erick Dowdle from a story he co-wrote with his brother Drew Dowdle.
It revolves around a serial killer's murders in Poughkeepsie, New York, told
through interviews and footage from a cache of the killer's snuff films.
The film premiered at the 2007 Tribeca Film Festival, but had a troubled release history; it was originally slated for
theatrical release by Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer in February 2008, but was removed from the release schedule.
The film had a brief video-on-demand release in 2014,
but remained unavailable on home media.
In October 2017, the film was released and
remastered on DVD and Blu-ray by Shout!
Factory via the newly-revived Orion Pictures.
The film explores themes of mask, pedophilia,
stockholm syndrome, suffering, sadism.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.